Previously on Marshals...
- [neighing]
- [Kayce] Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey!
- Stallion's moving on.
- He's Mom's.
You can't just erase
every memory of her.
I didn't cry
at my dad's funeral.
I was too overwhelmed
by the loss to actually grieve.
[Calvin] It was nice of
your husband and kid to drop by.
You know. building walls
shuts out the people
that you care about.
- [roaring]
- [yells]
[Weaver]
You saved my life.
Let me lend you some hands.
Well. good day for you.
You kept your badge
and you made a new friend.
Saddle up. cowboy.
♪ "Revelation"
by Ari Kaplan playing ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[neighing]
What part of evolve or die
do you not understand?
♪ Help me to find ♪
♪ The wisdom ♪
♪ Give me the light ♪
♪ On my darkest night... ♪
[sighs]
♪ I need a revelation ♪
♪ Mm... ♪
Here to check
on your dad's hands.
they're moving the herd.
I was out exploring.
Had a vague memory
of you promising
to give this newbie
an insider's tour.
Pretty sure I said "maybe."
So you'd rather wrestle
that horse than show me
what's so great about Montana?
Try and keep up. [clicks tongue]
♪ majestic music ♪
[Dolly]
Reminds me of the Pyrenees.
[chuckles] Alps. too.
[Kayce] Yeah?
You done a lot of traveling?
[Dolly]
Yeah. Growing up.
we'd take family trips
every summer and Christmas.
You?
I had to join the Navy
to see the world.
[Dolly]
And just think.
this was left by a glacier
10.000 years ago.
It's also the spot where I took
my brother Jamie's clothes
while he was skinny-dipping.
He had to ride home bare-assed.
[both laugh]
[sighs] Must've been a dream
growing up with
the world's greatest backyard.
Handle that horse pretty well.
Believe it or not.
there are stables in the city.
♪ gentle music ♪
[Dr. Ginsburg] You said
you'd been experiencing
some neck and shoulder pain?
Some tingling in the hand?
How long have you had
these symptoms?
Since the first door
I breached. I just...
I've learned to live with them.
How many deployments
did you have?
More than I can remember. literally.
Well. we'll run some tests.
try to find you some answers.
Okay.
♪ dramatic music ♪
[woman]
See you later.
[Jared]
Cal?
What are you doing here?
Belle hasn't mentioned
your team is
running down fugitive doctors.
- [chuckles]
- Hey. Jared.
Uh. nah. I was just. um.
getting a checkup.
Yeah. I was at a work lunch.
Should get back to the office.
Right. It's good seeing you.
Yeah.
♪ low. dramatic music ♪
Your dad make you
uproot your life
to move all the way out here?
[chuckles]
I'm a grown woman.
Can't make me do anything.
I'm here because I love him.
and because he made me partner
in his new cattle venture.
[Weaver groaning]
[Dolly]
Dad. what're you doing here?
[exhales]
[Weaver]
Kayce broke my leg.
Had to make sure
you were safe. pumpkin.
- [chuckles]
- I believe
you brought me a hat.
last time I saw you.
Allow me to return the favor.
[chuckles]
It's good to see you up
on your feet so soon. sir.
No days off on the ranch. right?
And I healed enough
I managed to bag an elk.
I figured I'd make dinner.
pay down my debt to you.
Well. I know better than to
refuse an offer from a Weaver.
[Dolly and Weaver chuckle]
[Weaver]
Great.
[up-tempo rock music playing]
[Maddie laughs]
Here... Here you go. Miles.
Uh. the tea was a little tart.
so I-I spiked it
with a sugar cube.
- Appreciate it.
- [chuckles]
♪ I keep the faith. oh. man ♪
♪ Million dollar
doubt about it... ♪
Feel bad rolling you
on Mom's night out.
[Belle]
Eh...
Jared and Braxton left
for a father-son camping trip.
so I got all night
to take your money.
Mm. Who you betting on?
After seeing Belle
as a biker chick.
I got no doubt
she's got some hustler in her.
- Mm.
- [Andrea chuckles]
My money's on Miles.
Broken Rock's luck is turning.
thanks to its guardian angel.
Sabrina. these are my teammates.
Belle and Andrea.
They helped find
the missing girls.
Well. look at you.
sharing credit.
You know.
for a former college athlete.
you have a pretty small ego.
"College athlete" is a stretch.
All state tight end
and linebacker. full ride
- to a D1 program.
- [Andrea] Damn. Miles.
I knew you played. but
I didn't know you were a player.
I wasn't. Dropped the ball.
Miles and the coach didn't
see eye to eye.
Dust Cloud being Dust Cloud.
I've mellowed.
Hopefully not too much.
- [clears throat]
- Nice meeting you.
Miles's friends.
Give me a call sometime. Miles.
♪ And if I don't win. hell.
I'll try again tomorrow... ♪
[Sabrina laughs]
All right. This does bring up
a very important question.
Are you dating anyone?
No. [chuckles]
[Miles clears throat]
You like someone.
It's complicated.
- [Andrea gasps]
- She's not from where I'm from.
- So?
- So. like my football career.
it's probably not meant to be.
[Miles clears throat]
I know. it was delicious.
I think I want to come back
next week.
- Yeah. We will. [chuckles]
- Yeah. good. Good. good. good.
I forgot the leftovers.
[Pauline chuckles]
Blake...
All right. I'm going back.
Shoot. I left my glasses inside.
Just be a minute.
[valet] I'll keep it running.
Your Honor.
[car alarm blaring]
♪ soaring. dynamic music ♪
♪
Good job. sir.
Most people overcook elk.
Mm. Dad's the chef
in the family.
I got an unwanted promotion
to house cook.
I can't compete with you.
How I feel
about you and your family
when it comes to ranching.
Hmm. Why he pays
a team of brainiacs
with ag degrees to help.
[Weaver]
Doing more than helping.
They've pointed me
toward some technologies
to up my chances for success.
Well. I was raised to believe
the old ways are the right ways.
[Weaver] From what I hear.
the old ways included
the Yellowstone never turning
a profit.
[scoffs] Well. the way of life
is the true reward
when it comes to ranching. sir.
[chuckles]
Not with my investors.
If-if I can put my thumb
on the scale.
why wouldn't I?
DNA marker testing
helped me pick
the most productive cattle
to start with.
and now.
I'm tracking them using RFID
to keep my labor costs down.
Sounds like a hefty
up-front cost.
That's why I spread the risk.
Offer each head
as an individual asset
folks can invest in.
That working capital
increases my valuation.
[chuckles]
You and my sister'd get along.
I'm in it
for the long haul. Kayce.
More land. more cattle.
That's how I attract
more investors.
I would love
to make East Camp
part of my operation.
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
You want to buy my ranch?
[wry chuckle]
Geez. Dad. give him dessert
before asking him into bed.
I'm direct when I see
something I want.
Hmm. Thank you for dinner.
Uh. let us help clean up.
No. dishes are one thing
I can handle in the kitchen.
I meant no. uh. no offense.
We can both come out winners.
Think it over.
♪ low. dramatic music ♪
- [sighs]
- Was that some sort of plan
to soften me up
so your dad could make an offer
on East Camp?
I was as blindsided as you.
It's why my family never talks
business at the dinner table.
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
We were having fun
until he ruined it.
Weren't we?
Yeah.
Thank you for a lovely day.
Good night.
Hey. Got something
you want to tell me?
About what?
Ghosting us at the bar
last night.
Ah. [scoffs] Yeah.
Day got away from me. My bad.
Uh-huh.
Hey. Gifford called.
We've got something.
Federal Judge Pauline Ayers
and her husband Blake
- survived a car bomb attack.
- [Calvin] Yeah. I saw that.
The valet wasn't so lucky.
You got any leads on a suspect?
[groans] A federal judge likely
has a long list of enemies.
Clint Gallo.
Threatened revenge ten years ago
when Ayers sentenced him
to prison
for the bombing
of a women's health center.
Paroled last month.
Missed a check-in
with his P.O. last week.
Well. that makes him a fugitive.
Yeah. The FBI's got the lead on
the bombing. but Gallo's ours.
Judicial protection falls under
the Marshals' purview.
Are we watching over Ayers?
And her family. until
her attacker's in custody.
Cowboy and I can hunt down
the ex-con while the rest of you
shack up with the happy family?
♪ dramatic music ♪
Yeah. Last thing we need
is an open season on judges.
[Calvin]
I know it feels like
we're punishing
the victims here. but...
but given the bomber
knew your pattern of life.
we're-we're gonna
have to restrict
your family's movements.
Your marshal doing
the security sweep is gonna
spook our neighbors.
Uh. you...
do you have any leads?
[Belle]
We're eyeing a violent convict
you sent away years ago.
Oh. Well. that
really narrows it down.
We're gonna do our best to stay
out of your hair. Your Honor.
Oh. knock that
"Your Honor" crap off.
Hey.
Oh. Magic City
Nonprofit of the Year
2023. Chiron's Care.
[Blake] I'm the. uh.
executive director.
We get medical equipment
to underserved communities
around the world.
He's the softie.
I'm the hard-ass.
[others chuckle]
Well. if you need
dental supplies.
I can connect you to my husband.
He's a do-gooder. too.
[Fallon] Franny says Lulu
wants the ticket
to MountainLoaf if I can't go.
The. uh. music festival
next month?
Yeah.
Well. honey. if you're
still under protection
by then.
we have failed at our job.
[Pauline] Even if you succeed.
Blake and I
haven't said that Fallon can go.
♪ dramatic music ♪
My mistake.
[Fallon sighs]
This is where
Gallo's girlfriend lives?
Guess she's got a kink
for convicts.
Okay. so. Gallo took a shot
at the judge
after serving ten years?
[Andrea]
Values vengeance over freedom.
- Seems like a trade you'd make.
- [indistinct chatter]
Hey.
Clint Gallo?
♪ intense. dramatic music ♪
[Kayce]
U.S. Marshals!
[Gallo groans]
[sighs] Tossed him
like an angry bronc.
You're sounding more Montanan
every day.
- [laughs. sighs]
- [sighs]
You know. much of my work
is confidential.
[Miles] The Fusion Center
won't break privilege.
they'll just analyze the threats
you've gotten.
[Blake]
Hope they're working in shifts.
Your husband give you
a hard time
for going after the worst of us?
It's a constant negotiation.
but we always find
common ground.
Unfortunately for me.
judges don't negotiate.
[chuckles]
♪ gentle music ♪
[Calvin]
Your Honor... Ma'am?
We're gonna need you to stay
where we can keep eyes on.
I need to use the bathroom.
[Calvin] Use your daughter's.
There's no windows.
Stay out of there.
I'm tie-dyeing a dress
for MountainLoaf.
[sighs] Don't get
ahead of yourself.
[Blake] We should let her go.
have some normal teenage fun
after all this.
Hey. you heard Mom.
No chance Maximum Pauline
shows me any leniency.
Great. I'm the bad guy. Again.
♪ melancholy music ♪
You think we should warn them
the last thing they want
is their daughter
picking sides between them?
She's got enough on her plate
with someone trying to kill her.
But if you know something
that affects somebody's family.
I mean.
you should say something. right?
Family drama should stay
in the family.
[Andrea]
Threatened the judge last decade
and enacted your vengeance
last night.
You sure can hold a grudge.
I'll give you that.
- Ayers is dead?
- Nope. but a valet is.
I was at Teresa's all yesterday.
She'll vouch for me.
Doesn't matter.
When the bomb went off
and when it was planted
are two different timelines.
I got better things to do
than settle some old score.
Way she dropped the hammer.
cops are getting
pretty lazy if they think
I'm the only one
dreamt of murdering her.
♪ dramatic music ♪
I'm trapped in my home.
like Elsa.
No one wants
to hear this. honey.
Maybe this is a blessing
in disguise.
A chance to put family first.
the way you talk about. Hmm?
That guy sure seems thirsty
for his wife's attention.
What's with your need to play
Dr. Phil with them?
Nothing. We just both know
that putting all in at work
can fracture relationships.
Speak for yourself.
- Fallon. no!
- [alarms wailing]
[Calvin]
Get down. get down!
- Away from the window.
- [gunshot]
It's okay. baby. You're fine.
Someone's trying to kill you.
Nothing is fine.
[banging on door]
[Belle]
Blue. blue.
[Calvin]
So? Any trace of the shooter?
[Belle]
Negative.
Only place shots
could've come from
is the parking garage
across the street.
[Miles]
Didn't find any casings.
Shooter cleared out too fast
to be on foot.
We're getting security footage.
Does Gallo's sheet have
any long guns work?
Kayce and Andrea apprehended him
well before
these shots were fired.
Okay. well.
if he's not our shooter.
then we can't still like him
for the bombing.
Only thing certain is that
the assassin knows
where the judge is. so...
Listen up. y'all.
Ayers family.
there's a change of venue. okay?
You're coming to our house now.
Local PD is coming in
to take over the crime scene.
I can hold here
in case anything comes up.
[Pauline] There must be some way
that you can keep me safe
and not make my family
feel like prisoners.
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
Hey. I know a place
off-grid. okay.
that we can tuck these two away.
Okay? But you're coming with us.
Yeah.
Okay. come on. y'all. Let's go.
It's gonna be okay.
Takes an assassination attempt
on a judge
for an invite to your place.
I think you're confusing
an order from Cal
for a social gathering.
Weaver Ranch?
I see who your social
invitations are reserved for.
[door opens]
[Calvin]
Blue. blue.
Blake. Fallon.
I want you to meet
Deputy Marshals Dutton and Cruz.
Apologies for the intrusion.
Oh. don't apologize.
I understand
how you must be feeling.
I believe you do.
What's that mean?
It means we're in good hands
with Deputy Marshal Dutton.
[Fallon]
Good. Then he can find
who's trying to kill Mom
and we can go home.
[Andrea] If Gallo isn't our guy.
then any new theories on who is?
Yeah.
FBI forensics have concluded
that the bomb from the car
is more commonly seen
in the African Sahel
than in domestic terrorism.
[Kayce]
Yeah. that type of bomb making
and sniper skillset
feels military.
Agree. That's why
we're cross-referencing
the judge's sentencing records
with military jackets. but
till we find that assassin.
y'all keep your heads down.
[door closes]
Was it Tom or Dolly
who came over?
[scoffs]
Sounds like we'll be here
for a while. You'll tell me.
- I'm doing a security sweep.
- [chuckles]
- [indistinct chatter]
- Okay.
[Park] Security cams caught
a red van entering the garage
15 minutes before the shooting
and exiting shortly after.
No plates. but we're
sending you the footage.
Take what we can get
at this point.
[Park]
And my team found these
hidden in the wall
near the bullet hits.
Looks like the judge's husband.
Why's a nonprofit director
need an alias?
[Calvin] I'll give you
some privacy. ma'am.
Well. judge is settled in.
You figured out if her husband's
Jason Bourne?
Only his real passport
has been used for travel.
Then why all the other
phony IDs?
Finances.
Account attached to one of them
shows money moving from Blake
through shell corporations
to Equatorial Guinea and back.
Wait. Equatorial Guinea's
part of the Sahel.
where the car bomb's
tradecraft points to.
Well. maybe
he's masking the payment
for a hit out on his wife.
You think he is a suspect now?
He was with her during
both assassination attempts.
I mean. being in the line
of fire's a hell of an alibi.
Okay. What's his motive?
I mean. the marriage has
run its course.
and he'd rather collect
life insurance
than face a judge
in divorce court.
I know a broken relationship
when I see one.
♪ dramatic music ♪
Do you have anything to eat?
Uh... Got some elk steaks.
I spotted some Uncrustables
in the fridge
for the non-cavemen.
[refrigerator door closes]
I'm having trouble
with cell service.
Downside of living
in the 19th century.
The. uh. porch might get you
a bar or two.
♪ somber music ♪
[sighs]
How you holding up?
Some psycho wanting my mom dead
is kind of messing with me.
We get it.
Both of our dads died
because of their job.
That's so awful.
[Andrea] I lost my dad
in the line of duty.
and Kayce's dad was
the governor.
They find their killers?
Chance to find my dad's gets me
out of bed in the morning.
People on social media
were obsessed
with trying to solve
your dad's murder.
Hmm.
- I don't think about it much.
- [Andrea] Oh. come on.
You go man on fire
for victims you've never met.
You're telling me you don't have
a list of suspects?
Heard something about...
private contractors.
[Fallon] Is it wrong
that I want something
bad to happen
to whoever's after my mom?
There's a big difference
between craving vengeance
and getting it.
[Andrea]
I think about getting it plenty.
This was my dad's.
I carry it on the off chance
I ever meet his killer.
But mostly it just gives me
a sense of control
over the thing that owns me.
[phone buzzing]
- [Kayce] Yeah?
- [Calvin over phone] Coyo.
husband's starting
to look shady.
He's got aliases.
international payments.
I think he could be involved.
Well. there's a twist.
I'm gonna need you
to feel him out. okay?
Yeah.
♪ suspenseful music ♪
Blake?
How could he be missing? He was
under your team's protection.
My marshals think that
he left on his own.
Fallon is his whole life.
He wouldn't.
Well. we have security footage
from your husband's
disappearance.
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
Does the name Joseph Petit
mean anything to you?
No.
Joseph Petit is an alias
your husband uses.
Alias? I don't follow.
Your husband keeps
false passports
in a wall in your home.
You aware of that?
And is there anything else
he could be hiding?
Are you investigating
my husband?
Should we be?
We pulled this
from surveillance cameras
on our colleague's ranch.
Seems like
he was expecting them.
[inhales shakily]
They kidnapped him?
Has he been the target
all along?
It's possible.
But why?
We were hoping you...
you might know. Your Honor.
My husband of 25 years
has been living
a secret life. so
clearly. I don't know anything.
[sighs]
[Calvin]
We'll give you a moment.
[quiet sobs]
[door closes]
Well. that was brutal.
Well. we had to tell her
the truth.
I know.
And we just unraveled
a marriage. and we still
don't have answers.
Maybe Blake's hard drive
will help.
My man.
Let me see.
Fallon. you want some company?
[Fallon] No. Just... [sighs]
give me a minute.
[door opens]
- [sighs]
- [door closes]
Poor kid. She's literally
worried sick about her dad.
Given that Blake was
grabbed nearby.
Cal wants us to clear out.
All Fallon knows
is that her father's missing.
That's all she needs to know.
♪ suspenseful music ♪
We found some information
we'd like to share with you.
Your husband attended
the opening of a clinic
in Equatorial Guinea
about six months ago. right?
- Yes.
- That clinic
was run by Luis Andeme.
He's an activist
against the repressive regime
of President Bindong.
So this is payback for Blake
giving medical supplies
to the resistance?
That hard drive contains
evidence showing Andeme
convinced Blake to use his
nonprofit infrastructure to
smuggle weapons for his cause.
What?
You-You're telling me
Blake's an arms dealer?
President Bindong's daughter
was killed last month. Car bomb.
[Belle] Made by the resistance
with explosives
your husband supplied.
And then. three days ago.
Blake received
e-mails from Bindong's henchmen.
threatening death
unless he turned over
information
about everyone
he has shipped weapons to.
[Calvin] Blake probably
overheard us discussing
the construction of the car
bomb. and he connected the dots.
contacted them to meet.
Trying to protect
you and Fallon.
[Calvin]
And when they get
what they need from him...
Can't you identify
these monsters?
FRS returns identities
that seem to be scrubbed
in ways often seen with people
who've done covert work
with the U.S. government.
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
Their files can be unclassified
with a warrant
signed by a federal judge.
Shall we?
- [raining]
- [thunder rumbling]
Finding you a secure location.
And my mom's worried
about a concert.
On it. Cal.
Guys in the red van
are Americans...
Rylan Hightower and Nate Porter.
Ex-Delta Force.
now private contractors.
They both did FID
for Bindong's forces in 2022.
Is their contracting group
out of Texas?
Unknown. but Hightower has
property near Clyde Park.
That might be
where they're headed.
[Kayce] That's only
a few miles from here.
What do we do about...
Blake doesn't have much time.
[sighs]
♪ tense. dramatic music ♪
- This is where my dad is?
- We're about to find out.
I can't handle this.
I'm freaking out.
[Andrea]
Fallon. it's gonna be okay.
DOJ wants to talk to these guys
about their work with Bindong.
so we need them alive.
Blake doesn't have time.
I'm going in now.
You stay with Fallon.
One is none. remember?
Especially against
special forces operators.
Cal and Belle are
ten minutes out.
You ever wish that help
would've gotten to your dad
ten minutes faster?
- [truck door opens]
- [exhales]
♪ suspenseful music ♪
[Porter] Give us some names
or fry some more.
[Blake]
Please. I told you.
I don't know. I don't know.
Let's help him remember. yeah?
U.S. Marshals!
[Blake grunting]
[Kayce]
You okay?
I will be
when you get the other guy.
♪ intense. dramatic music ♪
[gunshots]
[both grunting]
[coughs]
[panting]
[Calvin exhales]
It's just here.
[sighs]
Oh. thank God.
♪ gentle music ♪
You haven't said a word
to your dad.
What do I say?
Thanks for nearly getting Mom
shot and blown up?
I'd just be grateful
they're alive.
I am.
But...
...is my dad a monster?
I once took down this fugitive
my dad had put away.
The guy swore
my old man was corrupt.
It shook me up.
Do you think he was dirty?
I think that I would
love the chance to ask him.
No father's perfect.
And once you realize he was just
trying to protect you
in his own messed-up way.
your anger will fade.
I just hope that. if you ever
do decide to forgive him.
he's still around to hear it.
Hey.
[Belle]
I just closed the Ayers file.
Should we go join the others
at the Bullet?
Pass.
[sighs] Come on.
Is Maddie still
freezing you out?
You know. one of us
can order for you.
avoid any further
awkward interactions.
Look. go have fun
with your teammates.
Well. this is a pickle.
See. I really need
that buffer zone
between work and home
that you suggested.
but I can't leave you here
like this.
Bourbon? [whistles]
That's an aggressive choice.
Man. we just told the judge
half her life is a lie.
Move.
I mean. if that doesn't call
for hard stuff...
...I don't know what does.
[rock music playing]
♪ A soul that can't be tamed ♪
♪ An open road
that calls our names... ♪
[Miles] Dedicate your life
to someone. only to find out
you barely know 'em.
[sighs] A family like that
is the reason why
I remain eternally single.
[Miles]
Bulldogger's loss.
- [Andrea chuckles]
- What's next for you?
Bull rider? Rodeo clown?
No. What about you? When are you
asking out this mystery girl?
Probably too complicated
for it to ever work out.
That's how you know it's right.
I don't have a lot of experience
dating non-Native women.
Just be confident.
[Miles]
Not exactly my strong suit.
Any advice on asking out
women around here from a local?
Well. the last time
I asked out anyone.
I was in high school
and she was from Broken Rock.
If I'm gonna crash and burn.
might as well have my teammates
here to put out the flames.
She's here?
Here goes nothing.
♪ Mm. sit still ♪
♪ But got hard to leave.
ooh-way ♪
♪ There's nothing out there
that can make her stay ♪
♪ Be gone world... ♪
You guys need refills?
[Miles]
Um. sure.
[chuckles]
Also. uh...
I was wondering.
would you maybe like to go
on a date sometime?
With you?
Maybe.
I mean...
yeah. with me.
Yeah. I-I'd love to.
[chuckles] I was hoping
you might be interested.
I just thought maybe
you'd chicken out.
No way. I'm a confident guy.
Well. you must be.
asking out your boss's daughter.
♪ Loud and sweet ♪
[chuckles]
Maddie was maybe three.
and we went to. we went
to the San Diego Zoo. [laughs]
She lost her mind.
[both laughing]
And I was. I was tucking her in
that night. and...
she said.
"This is the best day ever."
Well. you know.
no one's childhood
stays frozen in time.
Look at Fallon.
She just found out her father's
the villain
in someone else's story.
What about Pauline?
I mean. Blake wasn't
who she thought he was. either.
- Mm.
- I mean. does their...
does their marriage survive?
[both chuckle]
You know how tough marriage is.
Would your marriage survive
if your...
husband was living
a secret life?
There's nothing
I don't know about Jared.
- [chuckles] Really?
- Really.
Given everything
that you shield from him?
You really think
a cop can't tell
you're sitting on something?
Come on. Out with it.
You have been weird all day.
Give it to me.
Look. it's not my place.
but I-I know that you would do
the same for me
if the situations
were reversed. so...
♪ dramatic music ♪
What situation?
I saw Jared with another woman.
[sighs]
He's supposed to be discreet.
What? Wait. that's it?
[sighs] Okay.
Not that I have
to justify anything.
but...
...people change.
You know. years go by.
My work undercover
kept us apart.
Things slipped... away.
Why... why stay together?
Keeping my family whole
for Braxton
is my priority.
[sighs]
Seems kind of lonely.
though. no?
[laughing]
That was a terrible idea.
[chuckles] Yeah. Sorry. uh.
the-the booze and long day.
[sighs] Yeah. Uh...
Let's just call it a night.
["His to Mine"
by Adam Sanders playing]
♪ If he's anything like me ♪
♪ That old boy
had to see it coming... ♪
[both laughing]
♪ And if you ask... ♪
Guy who doesn't drink
pining for the bartender.
Go figure.
♪ Anything.
I bet he doesn't... ♪
You really haven't
asked anyone out since Monica?
♪ I bet he's why your phone's
face down on the bar... ♪
Did your mom date
after your dad?
♪ If he was here
he'd tell me... ♪
Oh. now we're getting somewhere.
[chuckles] Does this have
anything to do
with the Weaver Ranch swag
at your house?
Hey. Dolly ambushed me.
[laughs] Really?
Drive-by date?
Oh. I underestimated this chick.
♪ A girl like you puts... ♪
Did you enjoy it?
As much as you and I focus
on avenging our dead...
guess we can betray them. too.
Hanging out with Dolly
felt like cheating on Monica.
I see.
♪ Worth the ride... ♪
Yeah. my mom dated.
Then she met a great guy.
and I realized
that she wasn't replacing my dad
in her heart.
she was just making room
for someone new.
What about your dad?
♪ Baby. take me to heaven... ♪
Uh. nothing serious.
He didn't have room
for anyone or anything else
other than anger
at losing my mom.
And do you think Monica
would want that for you?
♪ Just hit me
with that hurt... ♪
I'd love the chance to ask her.
♪ Before me. wherever he is ♪
♪ In the world tonight ♪
♪ I bet he's picking up pieces ♪
♪ A girl like you ♪
♪ Puts the good in goodbye ♪
♪ I bet you make it
look easy... ♪
[horse neighing]
[exhales]
You gonna get back
on that horse?
Not sure I'm ready.
I'm sorry about the other night.
I think I overstepped.
Call it a family trait.
Is another tour
out of the question?
It's just a horseback ride.
♪ Yeah. I know my heart
don't stand a chance tonight ♪
♪ But do what you did to his ♪
♪ It's yours for the breaking ♪
♪ Girl. I'll be just fine ♪
♪ So do what you did to his ♪
♪ To mine ♪
♪ Yeah. to mine ♪
♪ intense. percussive music ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm